805-403-7104 Danieljasongold@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/danieljasongold

Web developer and programmer equally proficient with front-end and back-end projects. Detail-oriented problem solver with a passion for iterating new features to create better user experiences. Brings leadership, teamwork and valued work ethic to solve technical challenges. Portfolio available at <u>dangold.me</u> and <u>github.com/landgod</u>.

EDUCATION

University of Washington, Seattle, WA

2019

CODING | SOFTWARE PROGRAMMING BOOT CAMP

University of California at Irvine, Irvine, CA

2016

BACHELOR OF ARTS: Drama, Theater Arts and Stagecraft

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, HTML, CSS/SCSS

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB

Frameworks: React, Hugo, Express, Node, jQuery

Additional Skills: Git, REST, OOP, JSX, AJAX/JSON

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Web Developer

June 2020 – Present

JAQUISH BIOMEDICAL, Seattle, WA

Current primary contributor and maintainer of codebase for www.jaquishbiomedical.com.

- Utilize JavaScript, Hugo, and Tailwind to improve upon and add to static e-commerce website.
- Write E2E tests with Cypress and troubleshoot deploys via Netlify.

Full Stack Web Development Tutor

November 2019 - June 2020

TRILOGY EDUCATION, Seattle, WA

Increased full stack web development skills and capabilities of working professionals as bootcamp students to learn and understand the material in software programming, coding and related technologies.

Coached working professionals weekly on all aspects of web development resulting in successful completion.

Programmer, Light Board | Master Electrician Technician

September 2018 – March 2020

IATSE, Seattle, WA

Provided technical support for theater productions throughout Seattle area to ensure effective theatrical lighting.

Programed effects, moving heads, and conventional lights, on ETC Eos Ti and Ion computer consoles.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

ThriftBuyer | github.com/LandGod/ThriftBuyer | ThriftBuyer.net

Developed a rating and review platform for B2C thrift store purchases to track product availability by enabling consumer reviews and recommendations.

- Built Node.js server running with Express and Handlebars to dynamically serve content.
- Created persistent data storage with MySQL and Sequelize, fully user searchable via category and geolocation.

Parent Trap | github.com/LandGod/Parent-Trap | evening-chamber-98293.herokuapp.com

Full stack project designed with React on Node Express server to create a family communication tool to track tasks and appointments for all members with text notifications and email reminders.

Partnered with a team of three programmers utilizing principles of object-oriented programming (OOP).

Super Realistic Hacking Simulator | github.com/LandGod/Word-Guess-Game | landgod.github.io/Word-Guess-Game Developed hang man game with comedic future-retro aesthetic in the style of a command line interface.

- Created with vanilla JavaScript, HTML and CSS.
- Utilized list of thousands of the most common English words and parsed using Python.